<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Angus Jellis</title>
    <link>https://angusjellis.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Angus Jellis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://angusjellis.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Github Migration (Short)</title>
      <link>https://angusjellis.co.uk/posts/migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angusjellis.co.uk/posts/migration/</guid>
      <description>Summary Our legacy SCM system had been in use since ~2015. Five years&amp;rsquo; worth of technical debt had built up (in terms of usrs, permissions, dependencies, naming conventions, etc).
I was given the task of planning and implementing our migration to GitHub.
Our old system was an absolutely critical system that supported the entirety of KPMG&amp;rsquo;s Engineering function, with around 600 users, and £millions of revenue dependent upon it.
There were around 3200 repos on the legacy system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://angusjellis.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angusjellis.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a DevOps Engineer based in Manchester.
My primary responsibilties involve building and maintaining my company&amp;rsquo;s Developer Productivity suite, using a mixture of vendor products and custom-built internal tools.
Outside of work, I&amp;rsquo;m a fitness enthusiast, a cryptocurrency evangelist/investor, a gamer, and I love getting to concerts (primarily heavy metal).
I&amp;rsquo;ve built this site as a static site, compiled using hugo, with the hugo tanka theme.
The site is deployed using a GitHub Actions Pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://angusjellis.co.uk/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angusjellis.co.uk/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Within my current role, I build internal tooling using Python and Typescript, with the tooling hosted on AWS.
I make use of Serverless functions to automate toil, while also leading the development of an application with a Flask backend (hosted on ECS) and a React frontend (hosted as a Jamstack deployment using a combination of Cloudfront &amp;amp; S3.)
I write CI/CD Pipelines in GitHub Actions &amp;amp; Jenkins (preferably on Actions), with all source code being held on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
